# HERON CAKIQI

Full Stack Engineer

### INFO

#### **PHONE**

+38344755183

#### **EMAIL**

cakiqiheron@gmail.com

# LINKS

**Github** 

CodePen

#### **SKILLS**

JavaScript

ReactJS

Redux

Node.js

Express.js

# **LANGUAGES**

Albanian

English

German

### **PROFILE**

A full-stack JavaScript developer since 2016 with a passion for the functionality of the front end. Through the past 3 years I have built lots of real world side projects and also participated in different university projects always using the latest web development technologies such as ReactJS, Redux, Node.js, express.js, an MongoDB.

# **EDUCATION**

# University for Business and Technology (UBT)

Information Systems

Oct 2013 — Present

All courses completed but not graduated.

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Manager, SKY TRAVEL L.L.C

Jan 2017 — Present

General Manager in a travel agency business.

#### Agent, SCARDIAN J.S.C.

Jun 2017 — Oct 2019

Insurance sales agent.

#### Computer Network Architect, Expert NSHT

Jun 2015 — Dec 2016

Built different data communication local area networks (LANs) on as need basis in different offices and work places.